<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on LOCD Learning on your own!</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on LOCD Learning on your own!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 12:16:17 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Background of the web</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 09:25:04 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Treeeeee MotherDucker Tim Berners-Lee, a British scientist, invented the World Wide Web (WWW) in 1989, while working at CERN. The web was originally conceived and developed to meet the demand for automated information-sharing between scientists in universities and institutes around the world.
On 30 April 1993, CERN put the World Wide Web software in the public domain. Later, CERN made a release available with an open licence, a more reliable way to maximise its dissemination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Background of the web</title>
      <link>/general/intro/background-of-the-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 09:25:04 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/general/intro/background-of-the-web/</guid>
      <description>The internet Birth of the internet Tim Berners-Lee, a British scientist, invented the World Wide Web (WWW) in 1989, while working at CERN. The web was originally conceived and developed to meet the demand for automated information-sharing between scientists in universities and institutes around the world.
On 30 April 1993, CERN put the World Wide Web software in the public domain. Later, CERN made a release available with an open licence, a more reliable way to maximise its dissemination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How does the internet work?</title>
      <link>/general/intro/how-does-the-internet-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 16:35:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/general/intro/how-does-the-internet-work/</guid>
      <description>How the Web works How the web works provides a simplified view of what happens when you view a webpage in a web browser on your computer or phone.
This theory is not essential to writing web code in the short term, but before long you&amp;rsquo;ll really start to benefit from understanding what&amp;rsquo;s happening in the background.
Clients and servers Computers connected to the web are called clients and servers. A simplified diagram of how they interact might look like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The internet</title>
      <link>/general/intro/the-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 16:35:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/general/intro/the-internet/</guid>
      <description>How does the internet work In short The Internet is the backbone of the Web, the technical infrastructure that makes the Web possible. At its most basic, the Internet is a large network of computers which communicate all together.
The history of the Internet is somewhat obscure (you can read more about it here). It began in the 1960s as a US-army-funded research project, then evolved into a public infrastructure in the 1980s with the support of many public universities and private companies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
